Facing foreclosure?
A short sale might be
your better option. Here's why.
Credit impact: Short sale drops
your score 50-150 points.
Foreclosure? 200-400 points.
Short sale wins.
Want to buy another home?
After a short sale: 2-4 years.
After foreclosure: 5-7 years.
Clear winner.
The debt? Short sales often forgive it
or make it negotiable. With foreclosure,
lenders can sue you for the difference
between sale price and what you owed.
Control: With a short sale,
YOU negotiate terms.
Foreclosure? The bank
owns the process.
Public records: Short sales show
as 'settled' or 'paid in full for less.'
Foreclosure is a permanent black mark.
Short sale beats foreclosure in
credit impact, future buying power,
debt forgiveness, control,
and public records.
SHORT SALE WINS ON
ALMOST EVERY METRIC
We specialize in short sales.
Free consultation - let's
explore your options.
📞 RepMotivatedSeller.com
We Buy Houses - Fast & Fair