What happens after you miss
a mortgage payment?
Here's the exact timeline.
After one missed payment,
you're in the grace period.
Late fees apply, but you're
not in foreclosure yet.
By month two, you're officially
in default. Your lender will start
sending notices and may report
to credit bureaus.
At 90 days, the lender files
a Notice of Default - this is when
pre-foreclosure officially begins.
You still have options!
Around month 5, a foreclosure
sale date gets scheduled.
But even now, you can
stop the process.
This 90-120 day window is critical -
you have the MOST options
during pre-foreclosure.
Your Action Window:
90-120 Days
MAXIMUM OPTIONS
The earlier you act,
the more options you have.
Get a free consultation now.
📞 RepMotivatedSeller.com
Free Consultation Today